<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>x.y.zheng</title>
    <link>http://xiaochenzheng.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on x.y.zheng</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="http://xiaochenzheng.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://xiaochenzheng.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://xiaochenzheng.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Dr. Xiaochen Y Zheng    I - left one on the picture - am a cognitive neuroscientist who&amp;rsquo;s always excited about the cognitive control processes in the brain, especially how they are shared between language and other cognitive systems.
Currently, I am a postdoctoral researcher at the Donders Institute for Brain, Cognition and Behaviour, investigating the neural and cognitive mechanism of inference in language and action planning. I joined the Motivation &amp;amp; Cognitive Control lab in 2019, working with Roshan Cools and Hanneke den Ouden.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://xiaochenzheng.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://xiaochenzheng.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>Contact me    I am usually quite reachable by email, xiaochen dot zheng at donders dot ru dot nl
Cannot risk any auto-reply? Then check the homepage and hope you will figure out how to find me faster. Good luck!!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://xiaochenzheng.github.io/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://xiaochenzheng.github.io/cv/</guid>
      <description>CV    Wanna know more? You can find my CV here.
Last updated 23 January 2024.
  #the-canvas { border: 1px solid black; direction: ltr; width: 100%; height: auto; display: none; } #paginator { display: none; text-align: center; margin-bottom: 10px; } #loadingWrapper { display: none; justify-content: center; align-items: center; width: 100%; height: 350px; } #loading { display: inline-block; width: 50px; height: 50px; border: 3px solid #d2d0d0;; border-radius: 50%; border-top-color: #383838; animation: spin 1s ease-in-out infinite; -webkit-animation: spin 1s ease-in-out infinite; } @keyframes spin { to { -webkit-transform: rotate(360deg); } } @-webkit-keyframes spin { to { -webkit-transform: rotate(360deg); } }  Previous Next &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Page:  /       window.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://xiaochenzheng.github.io/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://xiaochenzheng.github.io/projects/</guid>
      <description>Projects    Neural Mechanisms of Generalization and Novel Inference    The ability to generalize previously learned information to novel situations is fundamental for adaptive behavior. When seeing the word “un-reject-able-ish” for the first time, one can quickly infer its meaning by generalizing the knowledge of its constituent parts and integrating them based on certain abstract structural rules (e.g., the sequential order of the word parts). How do we generate novel, compositional meaning?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://xiaochenzheng.github.io/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://xiaochenzheng.github.io/publications/</guid>
      <description>Publications    2024    Parallel cognitive maps for multiple knowledge structures in the hippocampal formation
Xiaochen Y. Zheng, Martin N. Hebart, Filip Grill, Raymond J. Dolan, Christian F. Doeller, Roshan Cools, Mona M. Garvert
DOI PDF Open data Rebuttal (JoCN, rejected) Rebuttal (CerCor, accepted)
Domain-general cognitive control processes in bilingual switching: evidence from midfrontal theta oscillations.
Ningjing Cui, Vitória Piai, Xiaochen Y. Zheng
BioRXiv
2022    Neural oscillations of interference control in the aging brain: evidence from pictureword interference.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
